export const Questions = [
  {
    prompt: "A",
    optionA: "T",
    optionB: "F",
    optionC: "A",
    optionD: "B",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "B",
    optionA: "D",
    optionB: "B",
    optionC: "T",
    optionD: "C",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "C",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "D",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "D",
    optionD: "G",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "E",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "F",
    optionA: "F",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "G",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "G",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "H",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "I",
    optionA: "I",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "J",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "J",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "K",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "K",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "L",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "L",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "M",
    optionA: "M",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "N",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "N",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "O",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "O",
    optionC: "G",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "P",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "P",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Q",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "Q",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "R",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "R",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "S",
    optionA: "S",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "T",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "T",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "B",
  },
  {
    prompt: "U",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "U",
    answer: "D",
  },
  {
    prompt: "V",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "V",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "X",
    optionA: "X",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "A",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Y",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "Y",
    optionD: "D",
    answer: "C",
  },
  {
    prompt: "Z",
    optionA: "C",
    optionB: "H",
    optionC: "E",
    optionD: "Z",
    answer: "D",
  },
];
